<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Stage Stop Gun Shop | Indoor Range</title>
 <link href="https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//"/>
 <updated>2017-09-08T21:47:21-07:00</updated>
 <id>https://stagestopgunshop.github.io/</id>
 <author>
   <name>James Belk</name>
   <email>info@bornarts.us</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Beretta A400</title>
   <link href="https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//rifle-1008.html"/>
   <updated>2017-08-11T06:26:34-07:00</updated>
   <id>https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//rifle-1008</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/guns/rifle-1008.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Beretta A400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;beretta-a400&quot;&gt;Beretta A400&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BER A400 Action with Kick-Off Micro Core Recoil Reduction 12 Gauge 28 Inch Barrel 3 Inch Chamber Xtra Grain Walnut Stock Bronze Receiver 4 Round Features Kick-Off Micro Core recoil reducation. Self Compensation gas system, cycles all shells. B-LINK gas system. Steelium barrel with fiber optic sight. Bronze receiver. Xtra Grain walnut stock is 14.5 inches. Shim system for left/right, up/down stock adjustments. Reversible safety. Optima HP Choke (OBF): Full, Modified, Cylinder plus choke wrench. Includes hard case and extra stock shims.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Ruger American 6.5</title>
   <link href="https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//rifle-1007.html"/>
   <updated>2017-08-11T06:26:34-07:00</updated>
   <id>https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//rifle-1007</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/guns/rifle-1007.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ruger American 6.5&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;ruger-american-65&quot;&gt;Ruger American 6.5&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RUG American Predator Rifle 6.5 Creedmoor 22 Inch Threaded Barrel 5/8-24 TPI Moss Green Composite Stock 4 Round. Lightweight, Moss Green composite stock with modern forend contouring and serrations. Heavier tapered, threaded, cold hammer-forged barrel plus a factory installed one-piece aluminum scope rail. Ruger Marksman adjustable trigger with 3-5 pound user-adjustable trigger pull. Flush-fit rotary magazine. Visible and accessible tang safety. Power bedding integral bedding blocks. Soft rubber recoil pad. One-piece, three-lug bolt with 70 degree throw. Sling swivel studs included. Length of pull: 13.75 inches.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Kel Tec KSG</title>
   <link href="https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//rifle-1006.html"/>
   <updated>2017-08-11T06:26:34-07:00</updated>
   <id>https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//rifle-1006</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/guns/rifle-1006.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kel Tec KSG&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;kel-tec-ksg&quot;&gt;Kel Tec KSG&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The KSG™ is no ordinary tactical shotgun. Its dual tube magazines hold a dozen 3 inch, 12 gauge shells (plus one in the chamber), with the flexibility of switching between various projectiles. A patented downward ejection system makes it truly ambidextrous, while its 26.1 inch overall length, 18.5 inch cylinder bore barrel and 6.9lbs of weight make it is as compact as legally possible.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Benelli 828U</title>
   <link href="https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//rifle-1005.html"/>
   <updated>2017-08-11T06:26:34-07:00</updated>
   <id>https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//rifle-1005</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/guns/rifle-1005.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Benelli 828U&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;benelli-828u&quot;&gt;Benelli 828U&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A shotgun that feels and shoots like a Benelli from the moment you pick it up to the moment you break it open. When innovation and inspiration collided the 828U was born – the first over/under worthy of the Benelli badge. With the strength of steel and the weight of aluminum, the 12-gauge 828U has redefined the category. The 828U features a Patented steel locking system and plate, Easily removable trigger group receiver, Adjustable drop and cast, Ergonomic opening lever, Impulse activated ejectors. From butt to barrel, there is nothing about the 828U that hasn’t been rethought and improved.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Springfield M1A Socom II</title>
   <link href="https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//rifle-1003.html"/>
   <updated>2017-08-11T06:26:34-07:00</updated>
   <id>https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//rifle-1003</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/guns/rifle-1003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Springfield M1A Socom II&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;springfield-m1a-socom-ii&quot;&gt;Springfield M1A Socom II&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Socom II has a quad-rail that will allow you to mount whatever accessories your application requires. Maybe you need a light, laser or vertical foregrip – there’s ample space for all of these. Co-witnessed night vision and low-magnification optics are commonly found on rifles in this class, and the extended rail option gives you plenty of room for this. The SOCOM II has the same specially-engineered 16 inch barrel and proprietary muzzle brake as the SOCOM 16, so you can expect the same excellent recoil reduction and low muzzle rise. The two-stage military trigger and fast acquisition sights – a ghost ring rear aperture and XS Tritium front sight – are more features that make the SOCOM II a great choice for a tactical rifle.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Henry Golden Boy</title>
   <link href="https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//rifle-1002.html"/>
   <updated>2017-08-11T06:26:34-07:00</updated>
   <id>https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//rifle-1002</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/guns/rifle-1002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Henry Golden Boy&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;henry-golden-boy&quot;&gt;Henry Golden Boy&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Henry Lever Action .45-70 Government 22 Inch Octagon Barrel With Sights Blue Finish Brass Receiver Straight Walnut Stock Large Loop Lever 4 Round. Brass receiver fitted with a 22 inch octagonal barrel. Straight stock of American walnut. Brass buttplate endcap. Blued barrel with sights. Marbles fully adjustable semi-buckhorn rear sight with beaded front sight. Equipped with blued large loop lever.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Springfield Saint</title>
   <link href="https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//rifle-1001.html"/>
   <updated>2017-08-11T06:26:34-07:00</updated>
   <id>https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//rifle-1001</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/guns/rifle-1001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Springfield Saint&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;springfield-saint&quot;&gt;Springfield Saint&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SAI Saint AR-15 5.56mm NATO 16 Inch Chrome-Moly Barrel Melonite Finish Flip Up Rear Sight/A2 Front Sight Bravo KeyMod Handguard Bravo Pistol Grip Fixed Survivor System Stock PMAG 10 Round. AR-15 chambered in 5.56x45mm NATO and accepts .223 Remington. Direct impingement mid-length gas system; .750 diameter gas block. Upper receiver: aircraft grade 7075-T6 aluminum flat top with forward assist and M4 feed ramps, Type III hard coat anodized finish. Lower receiver: aircraft grade 7075-T6 aluminum Accu-Tite Tension System with Type III hard coat anodized finish. Sixteen inch chrome-moly vanadium barrel with 1:8 inch right hand twist rate and melonite finish. Springfield Armory proprietary GI trigger with nickel boron coating. Low profile flip-up sight, dual aperture rear sight, 1/2 MOA windage adjustable; fixed A2-style front sight. Bravo Company trigger guard, Mod 3 pistol grip and KeyMod PKMR handguard. Fixed Survivor System Stock. GI style charging handle. Carbine H heavy tungsten buffer system. M16 bolt carrier group with Carpenter 158 steel bolt, shot peened and magnetic particle inspected. Includes one 10-round Magpul PMAG Gen M3 magazine. Length: 35.75 inches. Weight; 6 pounds 13 ounces.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Sig Sauer 1911</title>
   <link href="https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//gun-1009.html"/>
   <updated>2017-08-11T06:26:34-07:00</updated>
   <id>https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//gun-1009</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/guns/gun-1009.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sig Sauer 1911&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;sig-sauer-1911&quot;&gt;Sig Sauer 1911&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SIG 1911 Full Size .45 ACP 5 Inch Barrel Low Profile Night Sights Stainless Steel Finish Blackwood Grips 8 Round - CA Compliant. Single action only. Features stainless steel frame and slide. Match grade barrel, hammer/sear set and trigger. Night sights. Front strap checkering. Checkered custom wood grips. Beavertail grip safety with speed bump, extended thumb safety, firing pin safety and hammer intercept notch. Frame and slide are dehorned for full-size carry option&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Glock 17</title>
   <link href="https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//gun-1008.html"/>
   <updated>2017-08-11T06:26:34-07:00</updated>
   <id>https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//gun-1008</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/guns/gun-1008.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Glock 17&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;glock-17&quot;&gt;Glock 17&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GLK Glock 17 9mm 4.49 Inch Barrel O.D. Green Finish Fixed Sights 10 Round. Steel slide and barrel combined with polymer receiver. Locked breech, trigger cocking action. Three safeties; trigger safety, mechanical blocking firing pin safety and drop safety. Natural grip angle and squared trigger guard. Packed in lockable plastic box with magazine loader, cleaning rod, cleaning brush and instruction packet. Fixed sights.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>FNH USA Five Seven</title>
   <link href="https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//gun-1006.html"/>
   <updated>2017-08-11T06:26:34-07:00</updated>
   <id>https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//gun-1006</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/guns/gun-1006.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;FNH USA Five Seven&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;fnh-usa-five-seven&quot;&gt;FNH USA Five Seven&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FNH Five-Seven 5.7x28mm 4.8 Inch Barrel Adjustable 3-Dot Sights Flat Dark Earth 10 Round. Newly designed adjustable rear combat sight gives the user the dependability of a rugged fixed sight and the versatility of an adjustable target sight together in one compact package. Slide features a polymer slide cover and frot and rear cocking serrations. Cold hammer-forged barrel. Chrome-lined chamber and bore. Polymer frame with checkered grip. Mil-STD 1913 accessory rail. Serrated trigger guard. Fully ambidextrous manual safety lever. Reveraible magazine release. Polymer magazine body with low-friction follower and polymer base pad.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Smith & Wesson 442</title>
   <link href="https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//gun-1005.html"/>
   <updated>2017-08-11T06:26:34-07:00</updated>
   <id>https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//gun-1005</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/guns/gun-1005.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Smith &amp;amp; Wesson 442&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;smith--wesson-442&quot;&gt;Smith &amp;amp; Wesson 442&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;S&amp;amp;W Model 442 Centennial Airweight .38 Smith &amp;amp; Wesson Special +P Double Action Only 1.875 Inch Barrel Matte Black Finish Fixed Rear Sight No Internal Lock 5 Round. Double action only. Integral front sight. Fixed rear sight. Synthetic grip. Aluminum alloy frame. Carbon steel cylinder.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Smith & Wesson 642</title>
   <link href="https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//gun-1004.html"/>
   <updated>2017-08-11T06:26:34-07:00</updated>
   <id>https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//gun-1004</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/guns/gun-1004.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Smith &amp;amp; Wesson 642&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;smith--wesson-642&quot;&gt;Smith &amp;amp; Wesson 642&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;S&amp;amp;W Model 642 Centennial Airweight .38 Special +P 1.875 Inch Barrel Matte Stainless Finish Double Action Black Grips 5 Round. Double action only. J-Small frame. Five round capacity. Internal hammer. .312 smooth target trigger. Serrated ramp front sight. Fixed notch rear sight. Black rubber grips. Aluminum alloy frame, stainless steel cylinder. Matte silver finish.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Kimber K6s</title>
   <link href="https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//gun-1003.html"/>
   <updated>2017-08-11T06:26:34-07:00</updated>
   <id>https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//gun-1003</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/guns/gun-1003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kimber K6s&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;kimber-k6s&quot;&gt;Kimber K6s&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kimber K6S weighs 23 ounces (with empty cylinder) is 6.62” in length nad has a cylinder capacity of 6.  It is stainless steel with a brushed stainless finish and a serrated backstrap.  The barrel is 2” in length.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Kimber Stainless Raptor II</title>
   <link href="https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//gun-1002.html"/>
   <updated>2017-08-11T06:26:34-07:00</updated>
   <id>https://stagestopgunshop.github.io//gun-1002</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/guns/gun-1002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kimber Stainless Raptor II&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;kimber-stainless-raptor-ii&quot;&gt;Kimber Stainless Raptor II&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No description present in the xl file. Need description. Send as a word doc only.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>